let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What does HTML stand for? ",
        answer: "C. Hyper Text Markup Language",
        options: [
            "A. Hyper Text Multi Language",
            "B. Hyper Tetx Multiple Language",
            "C. Hyper Text Markup Language",  
            "D. Home Text Multi Language",  
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "It is a markup language for describing web documents.",
        answer: "D. HTML",
        options: [
            "A. PHP",
            "B. CSS", 
            "C. USD",
            "D. HTML"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which <!__ TYPE> tag defines the document type as HTML?",
        answer: "C. !DOC TYPE",
        options: [
            "A. !HEAD TYPE", 
            "B. !HTML TYPE", 
            "C. !DOC TYPE", 
            "D. !TITLE TYPE" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What version of HTML is most currently used? ",
        answer: "D. HTML 5",
        options: [
            "A. HTML 2.0",
            "B. HTML 3.2",
            "C. HTML 4.01",
            "D. HTML 5"

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "The letter M in HTML stands for?",
        answer: "D. Markup",
        options: [
            "A. Machine", 
            "B. Memory", 
            "C. Multiple", 
            "D. Markup" 

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What elements define HTML? ",
        answer: "A. Whole Document",
        options: [
            "A. Whole Document", 
            "B. Body Document", 
            "C. Heading Document", 
            "D. Paragraph Document" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What is the HTML start tag? ",
        answer: "A. greater and less than symbol on both sides; html in between",
        options: [
            "A. greater and less than symbol on both sides; html in between", 
            "B. greater and less than symbol on both sides; html in between with a slash on the right", 
            "C. greater and less than symbol on both sides; html in between with a slash on the left", 
            "D. greater and less than symbol on both sides; html in between with a slash on both sides" 

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "How many versions HTML have? ",
        answer: "C. 6",
        options: [
            "A. 2",
            "B. 4",
            "C. 6",
            "D. 8"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What year created the old HTML? ",
        answer: "D. 1991",
        options: [
            "A. 1988",
            "B. 1989",
            "C. 1990",
            "D. 1991"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Who invented HTML? ",
        answer: "C. Tim Berners-Lee",
        options: [
            "A. Robert Cailliau ", 
            "B. Vint Cerf", 
            "C. Tim Berners-Lee", 
            "D. Jimmy Wales"            

        ]
    },
]